Finding Aid for the John Egerton Papers - Estate Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
John Egerton Papers - Estate Papers
1960-2014
University Archives
MSS.0849
14.7 linear_feet
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1963-1969 - Baldwin-McNeil (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - November 5, 1963-April 15, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1970 - Calvert-Wirth (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1971 - Allen-Griffin (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1971 - Hampton-Loyola (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1971 - McAdams-Pettigrew (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1971 - Richardson-Yeager (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - August 1, 1971-December 3, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1972 - Akir-Kirkpatrick (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1972 - Knoll-Russell (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1972 - Sanford-Yeakel (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 8, 1972-March 21, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1973 - Ansoff-Egerton (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1973 - Fettner-Loyola (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1973 - Magat-Wurzburg (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - March 19, 1973-October 5, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1974 - Armstrong-Grigg (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1974 - Hand-Popham (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1974 - Ray-Zimmerman (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - June 9, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1975 - Adams-Dunbar (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1975 - Egerton-Maurer (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1975 - Mitchell-Richardson (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1975 - Short-Wiltshire (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - June 17, 1975-December 19, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1976 - Alavi-Dunbar (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1976 - Egerton-Lowenstein (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1976 - McCauley-Wolfe-Novembeer 1, 19777 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1976 - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 28, 1976-December22, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1977 - Adams-Burgess (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1977 - Cahill-Hunt (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1977 - Inglehart-McGill (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1977 - Malkovsky-Stableski (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1977 - Smith-Viertal (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1977 - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - June 2, 1977-November 1, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1978 - Adams-Evans (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1978 - Gottlieb-McDaniel (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1978 - Malpas-Schlesinger (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1978 - Sheridan-Yeats (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1978 - Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 16, 1978-August 10, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1979 - Adams-Wiltshire (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1979 - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1980 - Atlas-Weir (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - September 8, 1980-November 24, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1981 - Blackwell-Herron (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1981 - Johnson-Wiltshire (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1981 - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 18, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1982 - Adams-Lewis (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1982 - McBrown-Young (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1982 - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 18, 1982-April 19, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1983 - Al-Amin-Ledford (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1983 - McCauley-Yancey (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1983 - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1984 - Adams-Lytle (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1984 - McMillan-Zelaya (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1984 - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - April 3, 1984-October 20, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1985 - Allnoch-Lipscomb (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1985 - McMillan-Yon (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1985 - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1986 - Alexander-Jester (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1986 - McCauley-Yantes (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1896 - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 24, 1986-November 26, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1987 - Ballard-Lehman (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1987 - McCarver-Wiltshire (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1987 - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 2, 1987-September 14, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1988 - Agerton- Ledford (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1988 - McLauren-Wilson (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1988 - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January21, 1988-July 20, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1989 - Adams-Loyd (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1989 - McCracken-Wirth (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1989 - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 21, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming - 1990 - Allen-Hurt (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1990 - Jester-Yardley (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence Incoming, 1990 - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - April 24, 1990-December 14, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1991 - Arp-Lewis (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1991 - MacLean-Wright (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 21, 1991-April 18, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1992 - Adams-Lichter (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1992 - Miller-Witherspoon (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1992 - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1993 - Ashmore-Kneebone (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1993 - Madison-Wilson (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1993 - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - May 13, 1993-December 3, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1994 - Albright-Fults (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1994 - Gorgon-Puffenbarger (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1994 - Reed-Young (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1994 - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 6, 1994-December 20, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1995 - Ahlschwede-Crippens (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1995-Davis-Humphries (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1995 - Ikard-Ross (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1995 - Saker-Young (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1995 - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1996 - Abadie-Fowler (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1996 - Gleaves-Murchie (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1996 - Noble-Zibart (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1996 - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1997 - Adams-Dye (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1997 - Evans-Meyers (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1997 - Parker-Zulan (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1997 - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 3, 1997-October 25, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1998 - Abadie-Lane (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1998 - McClure-Zirkle (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1998 - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - April 21, 1998-November 2, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1999 - -Adams-Lane (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1999 - McClure-York (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1999 - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - March 31, 1999-December 28, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2000 - Ballard-Lane (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2000 - McHaney-Wolf (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2000 - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - March 13, 2000-December 14, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2001 - Barnes-Mutize (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2001 - Paley-Williams (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2001 - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - April 9, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2002 - Baker-Woodward (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2002 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 4, 2002-December 21, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2003 - Adrian-Johnson (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2003 - McKee-Wiltshire (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2003 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - February 15, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2004 - Barnes-LaPrade (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2004 - McCall-Whitlow (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2004 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2005 - Clark-York (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2005 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - June 18, 2005-November 29, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2006 - Arnold-Ransome (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2006 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - October 27, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2007 - Arnold-Smith (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2007 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - January 9, 2006-December 14, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming 2008 - Beach-Reed (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2009 - Beach-Wolf (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - March 22, 2009-July 28, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Incoming 2010 - Brame-Wolfe (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - June 14, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2011 - Licitra-Mitchell (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2011 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2012 - Birdwhistell-Wilson (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - June 20, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2013 - Casey-Russo (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 2013 - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing - April 25, 2013-May 13, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Undated - Angell-Fooldt and Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Journalist-in-Residence
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1978-1979 - Virginia Tech - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1978-1979 - Virginia Tech - Course Outline and Notes (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1978-1979 - Virginia Tech - Course Resource Materials (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1978-1979 - Virginia Tech - Reflections on the Experience (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1997 — University of Texas - Course Notes (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1997 - University of Texas - Course Notes (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Journalist-in-Residence, 1997 - University of Texas - Course Research Materials (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Presentations
  - Presentations - Appalachian Writers’ Conference, 1977 and Trident Conference on Change, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Presentations - Friends of the Library, Vanderbilt University-April 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Presentations - Cumberland Valley Writers’ Conference-August, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Presentations - Cumberland Valley Writers’ Conference-July-August, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Presentations - Celebrations of Writers and Friends-Vanderbilt University, July, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Presentations - Florida Sun Coast Writers’ Conference, January, 1983 and February, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Presentations - Appalachian Writers’ Conference—August, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Presentations — Writers’ Workshop for Writers Over 57-August, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Presentations - The Once and Future South-March 27, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Presentations - Plowshare Chapel Writing Workshop-February, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Presentations - Bill of Rights Seminar, University of South Florida-March, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Presentations - Appalachian Writers’ Conference-July-August, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Presentations - The South in the Twentieth Century-January-March 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Presentations - Jesse Stuart Writing Symposium-April 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Presentations — Livingston Lecture, Atlanta History Center-May, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Presentations - Carson Newman College-March, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Presentations - Symposium for Professional Food Writers at the Greenbrier Hotel, West Virginia-March, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Presentations - News Channel Five Seminar, Nashville, TN-March, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Presentations - Symposium at Hampden-Sydney College-October, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Presentations - “Centering the South”, University of North Carolina, March, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Presentations - “Kentucky - Is It Southern?”, Eastern Kentucky University, September, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Presentations - Festival Blue Metropolis, Montreal, Canada, April, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Presentations - American South-Then and Now Symposium, University of Mississippi, November, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Presentations - Guest Lecturer, Celebrity Cruises, July-August, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Presentations - “The Story of Highlander Folk School”, Nashville Public Library, November, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Presentations - Natchez Literary and Cinema Celebration, February, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Presentations - The End of Southern History? Conference, Emory University, March, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Presentations - Highlander Rolling Seminar, February, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Presentations - Elder Hostel Mississippi River Trip, April, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Presentations - Tennessee State Museum Sit-ins Exhibit, May, 2009-February, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Presentations - Clarksville Arts and Heritage Development Council, July 24, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Presentations - Tennessee Mountain Writers Conference, March 25-27, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Presentations - Let the People Know: Spoken Word Census, May 30, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Presentations - Southern Festival of Books, October 15, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Presentations - Future Break. May, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Presentations - Southern Foodways Alliance Thirty-Thirteen Supper, September 15, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Presentations - Southern Foodways Alliance Symposium, October 19-21, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Presentations - History of Education Society, October 31-November 2, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Notes for Speeches, Part I (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Notes for Speeches, Part II (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Fellowships
  - Job and Fellowship Applications (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fellowships - Lyndhurst Foundation Prize, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fellowships - Virginia Center for the Humanities, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Projects
  - Projects - Southern Regional Task Force, 1972-1974 - Position Paper and Agenda (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Projects - Southern Regional Task Force, Egerton’s Report and Notes (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Projects - Southern Regional Task Force, Correspondence, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Projects - Southern Regional Task Force, Correspondence, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Projects - Writer Owned Publishing Cooperative - 1980-1984 Research (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Projects - Writer Owned Publishing Cooperative, Research (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Projects - Writer Owned Publishing Cooperative, Planning (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Projects - Writer Owned Publishing Cooperative, Correspondence, Incoming - Adams-Wigginton (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Projects - Writer Owned Publishing Cooperative, Correspondence, Outgoing - August 5, 1983-March 22, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Projects - Rugby Centennial Celebration, 1980 - Research (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Projects - Rugby Centennial Celebration, Correspondence, Incoming - Curzon-Paylor (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Projects - Rugby Centennial Celebration, Correspondence, Outgoing - October 8, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Projects - Rugby Centennial Celebration - Publicity and Egerton’s Speech (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Projects - Proposal for Series on Nashville Network, 1982 - Research (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Projects - Proposal for Series on Nashville Network, Title, “The Roots of Country Music” (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Projects - Proposal for Series on Nashville Network, Correspondence, Incoming - Healy-Smith (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Projects - Proposal for Series on Nashville Network, Correspondence, Outgoing, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Projects - Clarksville’s Bicentennial Story, 1984 - Consulting (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Projects - Southern Sampler at Aquinas,1987 - Final Menu (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Projects - Rugby Fund Raising Campaign, 1987 - Correspondence, Incoming - -Alley-Stagg (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Projects - Rugby Fund Raising Campaign, Planning (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Projects - Rugby Fund Raising Campaign, Printed Materials (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Projects - Wednesday Night Club, 1980s-2000s - Planning, Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Projects - Disney “Generations” Proposal, 1993 - Planning and Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Projects - Assisting South African Teacher to Attend MTSU, 1998 - Interview, CV, Photo (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Projects - “Partners of the Heart” video, 1999-2003 - Research and Planning (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Projects - “Partners of the Heart” video, Viewers Guide and Reviews (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Projects - Martin Luther King Memorial, 1999-2000 - Correspondence, Incoming, Bonior-Feldman (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Projects - Martin Luther King Memorial, Correspondence, Incoming, Feldman-Feldman (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Projects - Martin Luther King Memorial - Correspondence, Incoming, Feldman-Resnik (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Projects - Martin Luther King Memorial - Correspondence, Outgoing - July 16, 1999-April 27, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Projects - Martin Luther King Memorial, Newspaper Clippings (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Projects - Martin Luther King Memorial, Egerton’s Suggestions, undated (2 copies) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Projects - Veterans for Educational Opportunity, 1997-2001, Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Projects - Veterans for Educational Opportunity - Clippings (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Projects - Ledford Foundation vs. Appalachian College Association, 2000-2002 - Contracts and Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Projects - “They Closed Our Schools” video, 2000-2003 - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Projects - “They Closed Our Schools” video, Planning (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Projects - Ned Scott Archive, 2000 - Proposal (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Projects - Running for Office, 2000 - Correspondence, Incoming - Embrey-Pratt (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Projects - Running for Office, Correspondence, Outgoing, April 11, 2000-April 13, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Projects - Running for Office, Research and Planning (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Projects - Running for Office, Legal Documents (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Projects - Running for Office, Clippings (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Projects - Plan of Nashville, 2002 - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Projects - Plan of Nashville, Nashville History Timeline (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Projects - Proposed “Music Czar” for “Music City”, 2003 - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Projects - -Proposed “Music Czar” for “Music City”, Research (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Projects - Suppport for Donald Beisswenger, 2004 - Correspondence, Incoming - Beisswenger-Martin (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Projects - Support for Donald Beisswenger, Beisswenger’s Prison Diary (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Projects - Support for Donald Beisswenger, Book Proposal (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Projects - Health Care Issues, 2003-2005 - Correspondence, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Projects - Health Care Issues, North Carolina’s Project Access Policy (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Projects - Health Care Issues, Research (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Projects - Health Care Issues, Nashville’s “Bridges to Care” (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Projects - Health Care Issues, Egerton’s Commentary on TennCare (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Projects - Progressive Politics, 2007 - Tennessee Alliance for Progress (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Projects - Harmon Wray, Prisoner Advocate, 2007 - Correspondence, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Projects - Harmon Wray, Prisoner Advocate, Correspondence, Incoming - Robinson—Wilson (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Projects - Harmon Wray, Prisoner Advocate, Correspondence, Outgoing, May 8, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Projects - Harmon Wray, Prisoner Advocate, Obituary and Tributes (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Projects - Habitat for Humanity, 2008 - Research and Publicity (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Projects - Southern Food and Beverage Museum, 2008-2012 - Correspondence, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Projects - Southern Food and Beverage Museum, Correspondence, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Projects - Southern Food and Beverage Museum, Planning (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Projects - Southern Food and Beverage Museum, Publicity (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Correspondence, Incoming - Beats-Terry (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Projects - Little Roc Film Project, 2009-Correspondence, Outgoing—May 10, 2009-October 8, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Planning (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Interviews (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Interviews (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Research (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Research (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Egerton’s Notes (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Projects - Little Rock Film Project, 2009 - Film Proposal (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Projects - Brooks Fund History Project - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Projects - Brooks Fund History Project - Procedures (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Projects - Brooks Fund History Project - Interview with John Egerton (Box 13, Folder 14)